Okay, so Schedule Management Part 2 then
is Lesson 6.
So these are the learning objectives then
for Lesson 6.
One of the biggest things
we're going to be covering
in this section is the
Critical Path method.
There are several videos on Critical Path
method, so you need to understand.
So one of the major
objectives is to understand
all the steps involved in
the Critical Path method.
So the forward pass and the backward pass,
understanding all the
different types of float.
So we will be covering
all of that, so make sure
that you do understand
the critical path method.
Also, we'll be talking about other tools
such as resource optimization, right?
So you need to understand what the
resource optimization techniques are.
Also, there's a different approach.
Agile has a very different approach to
schedule management, right, then predictive.
So you need to appreciate, again,
the difference between the Agile release
planning and predictive schedule planning,
two very different approaches.
And then we'll also talk about two
important tools and techniques in Agile,
two important agile tools
and techniques call the
iteration burn down chart
and the iteration burnup chart.
So you need to be able to understand them.
You need to be able
to interpret the iteration
burn down chart and the burn up chart.